{
    "subject": "resource/Sidi_Ouriache",
    "predicate": "property/lats",
    "object": "20",
    "human_readable": "The latitude of Sidi Ouriache is 20.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9280551671981812,
            "question": "What is the latitude of Sidi Ouriache?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8560935258865356,
            "question": "Could you tell me the geographical coordinates of Sidi Ouriache?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106054663658142,
            "question": "What number represents Sidi Ouriache's latitude?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957528233528137,
            "question": "Using latitude as a reference, where is Sidi Ouriache in relation to other places?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855228781700134,
            "question": "If you were traveling to Sidi Ouriache, what latitude would you use for navigation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7805039286613464,
            "question": "What is Sidi Ouriache's position on a map based on latitude?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6354231834411621,
            "question": "Where is Sidi Ouriache situated geographically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6177389025688171,
            "question": "How far north or south from the equator is Sidi Ouriache?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600664615631104,
            "question": "Is Sidi Ouriache located in the northern or southern hemisphere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43508392572402954,
            "question": "At what degrees north or south is Sidi Ouriache located?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The latitude of Sidi Ouriache is 20.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1100_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sidi Ouriache located in the northern or southern hemisphere?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1100_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How far north or south from the equator is Sidi Ouriache?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1100_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Sidi Ouriache situated geographically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1100_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1100_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states the latitude of Sidi Ouriache is 35.1862547, not 20.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided does not support the triple that the latitude of Sidi Ouriache is 20. According to the context, the exact geographical coordinates (latitude and longitude) of Sidi Ouriache are given as 35.1862547, -1.5087605."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, the exact geographical coordinates for Sidi Ouriache are 35.1862547, -1.5087605. The latitude given in the query is 20, which does not match the correct latitude of Sidi Ouriache. Therefore, the statement \"The latitude of Sidi Ouriache is 20\" is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}